const List<Map<String, dynamic>> JSQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "What is JavaScript primarily used for?",
    "options": [
      "A. Designing website layout",
      "B. Adding interactivity to web pages",
      "C. Creating server-side logic",
      "D. Styling web pages"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. Adding interactivity to web pages",
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can JavaScript code be placed in an HTML file?",
    "options": [
      "A. Only in the <head> section",
      "B. Only in the <body> section",
      "C. Either in the <head> or <body> sections",
      "D. Only in external files"
    ],
    "Answer": "C. Either in the <head> or <body> sections",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method is NOT recommended for outputting content in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. document.getElementById().innerHTML",
      "B. document.write()",
      "C. window.alert()",
      "D. window.print()"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. document.write()",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. let x = 10;",
      "B. variable x = 10;",
      "C. declare x = 10;",
      "D. const x == 10;"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. let x = 10;",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following operators is used for multiplication in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. +=",
      "B. *=",
      "C. /=",
      "D. -="
    ],
    "Answer": "B. *=",
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct way to declare a string in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. let car = 'Toyota';",
      "B. let car == Toyota;",
      "C. let car := 'Toyota';",
      "D. let car : Toyota;"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. let car = 'Toyota';",
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the following JavaScript code return?\n`let result = myFunction(4, 3);`",
    "options": [
      "A. 7",
      "B. 12",
      "C. Error",
      "D. undefined"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. 12",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript data type?",
    "options": [
      "A. String",
      "B. Number",
      "C. Boolean",
      "D. Character"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Character",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid if statement in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. if (x > 10) then { ... }",
      "B. if x > 10 { ... }",
      "C. if (x > 10) { ... }",
      "D. if x > 10 then { ... }"
    ],
    "Answer": "C. if (x > 10) { ... }",
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you add a single-line comment in JavaScript?",
    "options": [
      "A. <!-- This is a comment -->",
      "B. // This is a comment",
      "C. /* This is a comment */",
      "D. # This is a comment"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. // This is a comment",
  },
];
